<?xml version="1.0" ?> 
<TrollAttack hacked="true">
	<room>
		<vnum>1</vnum>
		<east>2</east>
		<description>Tapestries are everywhere in this large room.   The scent of newly forged metal wafts through the air in what appears to be an entrace to a new world. The world of Lythia awaits. Type "?" or "help" to find out some of the basic commands.  When you are ready, type "east" to begin your adventure.</description>
		<title>Main Room</title>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>2</vnum>
		<west>1</west>
		<east>3</east>
		<title>Second Room</title> 
		<description>The second room, this room is not as decorative as the first room, but in its lack of elegance comes efficiency.  To the east wall there is a bookcase.  In the middle of the room there is a wide table covered in weapons. A large man wearing battle regalia stands at attention, holding a large sword in his hand. He states: "Here, this may be needed on the journey ahead."  You can get the sword by typing "get sword".    </description>
		<item>1</item>
		<item>1</item>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>3</vnum>
		<south>4</south>
		<north>6</north>
		<west>2</west>
		<title>Entering The World</title>
		<description>Now that you have equipped yourself with some basic weapons and have familiarized yourself with some of the controls, you are ready to enter the world.  Be careful and remember to have some fun!  Comments to the creator can be sent to trollattack@mortalpowers.com</description>
		<mobile>1</mobile>
		<mobile>1</mobile>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>4</vnum>
		<north>3</north>
		<east>5</east>
		<title>Tim's Playhouse</title>
		<description>Welcome to tim's playhouse!</description>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>5</vnum>
		<west>4</west>
		<title>Tim's Den</title>
		<description>This is Tim's den.  You may know Tim by him by his alter ego "The Duke of Awesome."  His room is sparsely decorated, save for the giant bronze statue of hisself flexing provocatively.  Upon his walls one can gaze upon a brilliant mural, capable of overwhelming one's senses and possibly even two's.</description>
		<mobile>3</mobile>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>6</vnum>
		<south>3</south>
		<east>7</east>
		<title>Main Adventure</title>
		<description>You have entered the main adventure, from here on out exploring, roleplaying, and common sense will be your best allies as you fight demons and attempt to beter yourself in the world of TrollAttack!</description>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>7</vnum>
		<west>6</west>
		<east>8</east>
		<title>Branching Path</title>
		<description>The main path branches here into three distinct trails.  The path to the north seems to take you to a large city.  The path to the east seems to take you into a grand forest.  The path to the south shall take you to what appears to be a small ocean village.  Currently all three paths are blocked by what appears to be a magical shield.</description>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>8</vnum>
		<west>7</west>
		<south>9</south>
		<title>Outside The Forest</title>
		<description>Just outside of the large forest to the east, you see another path leading off to the south.</description>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>9</vnum>
		<north>8</north>
		<title>Welcome</title>
		<description>As you enter the realm you have a strange feeling, you can sense that these realms are not happy ones. A plague upon the land. In the distance you see trolls, walking near the bodies of the dead. The scent of evil trolls is in the air.</description>
		<south>10</south>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>10</vnum>
		<title>To The South</title>
		<description>The surrounding bushes here are coated with blood. Dismembered human carcasses remain on the floor.</description>
		<north>9</north>
		<east>12</east>
		<south>11</south>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>11</vnum>
		<title>Outside the Village</title>
		<description>Numerous more carcasses litter the ground. You see small foot prints in the dirt. These footprints lead south, into the village.</description>
		<north>10</north>
		<east>13</east>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>12</vnum>
		<title>Small Cabin</title>
		<description>The inside of this cabin is filled with furniture. It is difficult to manuver from one end of the room to the other. The unlucky previous owner's remains litter the room. Need a cabin?</description>
		<west>10</west>
		<mobile>2</mobile>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>13</vnum>
		<title>North of The Village</title>
		<west>11</west>
		<east>14</east>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>14</vnum>
		<title>North of The Village</title>
		<west>13</west>
		<south>15</south>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>15</vnum>
		<title>Main Street</title>
		<north>14</north>
		<west>16</west>
		<south>18</south>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>16</vnum>
		<title>Main Street</title>
		<east>15</east>
		<south>17</south>
		<west>21</west>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>17</vnum>
		<title>The Baker's Emporium</title>
		<north>16</north>
		<mobile>5</mobile>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>18</vnum>
		<title>The Candle Stick Maker's Emporium</title>
		<north>15</north>
		<mobile>4</mobile>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>19</vnum>
		<title>Main Street</title>
		<west>15</west>
		<east>20</east>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>20</vnum>
		<title>Main Street</title>
		<west>19</west>
	</room>
	<room>
		<vnum>21</vnum>
		<title>Tangel Square</title>
		<east>16</east>
	</room>
</TrollAttack>