<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><TrollAttack><area><low>1500</low><high>1799</high><filename>Nightshade.xml</filename><name>Nightshade's Area In Progress</name><clicks>8</clicks><frozen>true</frozen></area><room><vnum>1500</vnum><title>Mountain Trail</title><description>This narrow trail has been worn smooth by countless years of travels.  The untraveled ground around the trail looks uneven but settled.  The trail rises up to the east.</description><east><vnum>1501</vnum></east><west><vnum>2021</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1501</vnum><title>Mountain Trail</title><description>This narrow trail has been worn smooth by countless years of travels. The untraveled ground around the trail looks uneven but settled. A small wood sign lies broken beside a tree. The writing has long since worn away.</description><east><vnum>1502</vnum></east><west><vnum>1500</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1502</vnum><title>Mountain Trail</title><description>The trail branches into two smaller paths.  The path to the east is wider and more worn the path north.</description><east><vnum>1504</vnum></east><west><vnum>1501</vnum></west><north><vnum>1503</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1503</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>This ridge extends off to the southeast.  Roots and rocks extend out from the mountainside that would provide enough footing to climb up.</description><south><vnum>1502</vnum></south><up><vnum>1505</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1504</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1504</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>This ridge extends off to the northwest.  Roots and rocks extend out from the mountainside that would provide enough footing to climb up.</description><west><vnum>1502</vnum></west><up><vnum>1506</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1503</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1505</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>There is a short dropoff here that extends off to the southeast.  There are plenty of roots and rocks extending out from the mountainside for a safe decent to the bottom of the ridge.</description><east><vnum>1507</vnum></east><down><vnum>1503</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1506</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1506</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>There is a dropoff here that extends off to the northeast. There are plenty of roots and rocks extending out from the mountainside for a safe decent to the bottom of the ridge.</description><east><vnum>1509</vnum></east><north><vnum>1507</vnum></north><south><vnum>1511</vnum></south><down><vnum>1504</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1505</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1507</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>The ground is rough and rocky as it rises twords the mountains in the northeast. There is a short tree that growing out of a large sheet of bedrock.</description><east><vnum>1508</vnum></east><west><vnum>1505</vnum></west><north><vnum>1514</vnum></north><south><vnum>1506</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1508</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>The earth is very uneven here. The are several large rock formations here. Two rocks in particular extend out of the groud to look like a pair of rabbit ears.</description><east><vnum>1540</vnum></east><west><vnum>1507</vnum></west><north><vnum>1515</vnum></north><south><vnum>1509</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1509</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>There are several large rock formations on this rugged ground.  A small group of bushes has grown out of some loose gravel.  To the east, the mountainside looks like a sheer, unclimbable cliff.</description><west><vnum>1506</vnum></west><north><vnum>1508</vnum></north><south><vnum>1510</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1510</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>The groud is covered with rocks and boulbers.  A few patchs of dry bushes are growing out of the bedrock.</description><east><vnum>1512</vnum></east><west><vnum>1511</vnum></west><north><vnum>1509</vnum></north><south><vnum>1517</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1511</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>Sheer walls of rock to the south and west tower over you. There is a small circle of stones around a pit of ash. The coals are cool to the touch.</description><east><vnum>1510</vnum></east><north><vnum>1506</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1512</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>Whistling can be heard as a breeze travels over this small gorge. The rock walls to the north and south are bright red and orange.</description><east><vnum>1513</vnum></east><west><vnum>1510</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1513</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>The ground here is rough and the faint sound of running water can be heard coming from the east.</description><east><vnum>1520</vnum></east><west><vnum>1512</vnum></west><north><vnum>1522</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1514</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>A sheer wall of rock towers over you to the west. It does not appear to be climbable. The faint sound of running water can be heard to the north.</description><east><vnum>1515</vnum></east><north><vnum>1530</vnum></north><south><vnum>1507</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1515</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>The ground mountainside is fairly steep here. The ground rises twords the East. The the faint sound of running water can be heard coming from the north.</description><east><vnum>1526</vnum></east><west><vnum>1514</vnum></west><north><vnum>1531</vnum></north><south><vnum>1508</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1516</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>This steep path winds up the mountainside. The path can be seen further down to the southeast.</description><up><vnum>1517</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1519</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1517</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>A small rocky trail leads to the north. A long steep path can be seen looking down to the southeast.</description><north><vnum>1510</vnum></north><down><vnum>1516</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1518</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>This path travels sharply upward to the northwest.  This narrow path can be seen further down to the southeast.</description><up><vnum>1519</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1549</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1519</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>This path travels steeply to the northwest. This narrow path can be seen further down to the southeast.</description><down><vnum>1518</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1516</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1520</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>A long cliff protrudes from the mountainside. It seems to extend off to the northwest. There is a large arrangment of boulders beside a tree that would make climbing the cliff fairly easy.</description><west><vnum>1513</vnum></west><up><vnum>1521</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1522</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1521</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground drops off near a cliff that extends off to the northwest.  A large formation of rocks below would make climbing down an easy task. The faint sound of running water lingers in the air.</description><east><vnum>1554</vnum></east><north><vnum>1536</vnum></north><south><vnum>1537</vnum></south><down><vnum>1520</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1523</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1522</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>A long cliff protrudes from the mountainside that extends off to the north and southeast.  It does not look very difficult to climb.</description><north><vnum>1524</vnum></north><south><vnum>1513</vnum></south><up><vnum>1523</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1520</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1523</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground drops off near a cliff that extends from the north to the southeast. It does not like it would be difficult to climb down. A small path to the west looks to travel steeply up the mountainside. The faint sound of running water can be heard coming from the east.</description><east><vnum>1536</vnum></east><west><vnum>1546</vnum></west><north><vnum>1525</vnum></north><down><vnum>1522</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1521</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1525</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground here drops off near the edge of a cliff. It seems to extend to the south and northwest. There is a large sheet of bedrock that has either fallen or been placed to form a ramp down. The faint sound of running water that can be heard off to the east.</description><east><vnum>1535</vnum></east><north><vnum>1532</vnum></north><south><vnum>1523</vnum></south><down><vnum>1524</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1527</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1526</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>A long cliff protrudes from the mountainside extending fom thr southeast to the north. There does not appear to be an easy way to scale the cliff.</description><west><vnum>1515</vnum></west><north><vnum>1528</vnum></north><south><vnum>1540</vnum></south><southeast><vnum>1524</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1527</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground here drops off near the edge of a cliff. There does not appear to be a safe way to get to the bottom of the ridge. The faint sound of running water lingers in the air.</description><east><vnum>1532</vnum></east><north><vnum>1529</vnum></north><southeast><vnum>1525</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1528</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>A long cliff extending off to the south protrudes from the mountainside. It looks possible to climb up where a small part of the rick shelf has broken off.</description><west><vnum>1531</vnum></west><south><vnum>1526</vnum></south><up><vnum>1529</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1529</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground here drops off near the edge of a cliff. It looks possible to climb down where a small part of the rock shelf has broken off. The mountain rises steeply off to the east. The faint sound of running water fills the air.</description><north><vnum>1533</vnum></north><south><vnum>1527</vnum></south><down><vnum>1528</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1530</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>The bluffs here consist of sharp rocks and hidden dropoffs. Three paths look like they are travelable. Rushing water can be heard to the north.</description><east><vnum>1531</vnum></east><north><vnum>1562</vnum></north><south><vnum>1514</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1531</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>These bluffs consist of large boulders, steep dropoffs and course bedrock. There is an arrow carved into on the boulders pointing twords the south. Rushing water can be heard to the north.</description><east><vnum>1528</vnum></east><west><vnum>1530</vnum></west><north><vnum>1561</vnum></north><south><vnum>1515</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1532</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>The ground here is jagged and sharp with hidden dropoffs. A sheer wall of rock to the north towers over you.  The sound of rushing water can be heard to the east.</description><east><vnum>1556</vnum></east><west><vnum>1527</vnum></west><south><vnum>1525</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1533</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>The ground here is uneven and loose. A trail of blood leads off to the north. The sound of rushing water fills the air, but it is difficult to determine where it is coming from.</description><east><vnum>1534</vnum></east><west><vnum>1561</vnum></west><north><vnum>1560</vnum></north><south><vnum>1529</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1534</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>The ground here is loose and uneven. To the south, there is a trail that rises sharply up the mountain. The sound of rushing water fills the air, but it is diffuclt to determine which direction if is coming from.</description><east><vnum>1558</vnum></east><west><vnum>1533</vnum></west><north><vnum>1559</vnum></north><south><vnum>1541</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1535</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>These bluffs consist primarily of sharp rocks and concealed holes. A boot is stuck under one of the boulders. There is no sign of who was wearing it. The sound of rushing water fills the air, but it is difficult to determine which direction it is coming from.</description><west><vnum>1525</vnum></west><north><vnum>1556</vnum></north><south><vnum>1536</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1536</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>The bluffs here are a maze of sharp rocks and dropoffs. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the east.</description><east><vnum>1611</vnum></east><west><vnum>1523</vnum></west><north><vnum>1535</vnum></north><south><vnum>1521</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1537</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>This path is barely large enough for even a single person to walk. This walkway appears to be stable despite the precarious location. The sound of flowing water is carried by a slight breeze.</description><east><vnum>1538</vnum></east><north><vnum>1521</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1538</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>The ground here is loose and uneven. A lone tree beside a small hole has a strange symbol carved into it. A claming breeze carries the sound of rushing water from the northeast.</description><east><vnum>1553</vnum></east><west><vnum>1537</vnum></west><north><vnum>1554</vnum></north><south><vnum>1539</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1539</vnum><title>The Bluffs</title><description>There is an unatural tree growing out of a large sheet of bedrock here. The leaves of the tree are a rich, deep purple. The tree only stands about shoulder height, but its thick trunk gives it an ancient appearence. Several flowers of the same deep purple have bloomed on it's branches. The sound of rushing water can be heard all around as a gentle breeze circles around the tree.</description><east><vnum>1552</vnum></east><north><vnum>1538</vnum></north><south><vnum>1551</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1540</vnum><title>Foothills</title><description>This trail runs along a mountain face. A smaller path branches off towards the north. There is a small holenew and old tree that leads down into the mountain.</description><east><vnum>1524</vnum></east><west><vnum>1508</vnum></west><north><vnum>1526</vnum></north><down><vnum>1695</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1541</vnum><title>Nearing A Mountain Peak</title><description>This small path leads steeply up to one of the many mountain peaks. It appears to have been well traveled.</description><north><vnum>1534</vnum></north><up><vnum>1542</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1542</vnum><title>Mountain Peak</title><description>From up here there is a spectacular view of the Breezy Cliffs. A great river flows eastward in the north. It turns southward and passes just to the east of this sumit. From there it travels southward. To the west, there is a clear view of the foothills and parts of the northren bluffs. Across the river to the north the Rocky Highlands can be seen. Across the river to the west you can see the Cliffs. To the south, more of the bluffs can be seen along the riverside.</description><down><vnum>1541</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1543</vnum><title>Nearing A Mountain Peak</title><description>This small path leads steeply up to one of the many mountain peaks. It appears to have been well traveled.</description><north><vnum>1669</vnum></north><up><vnum>1544</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1544</vnum><title>Mountain Peak</title><description>From this mountain peak there is a clear view of the rough terrain below. A great river runs from the north to the west, where it then turns south. Across the river to the northwest are the Breezy Cliffs. Across the river to west are the western foothills. Around the base of this mountain is Breezy Pass, which is said to be the path between the bridge directly to north and the bridge directly to west of this peak.</description><down><vnum>1543</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1545</vnum><title>Nearing A Mountain Peak</title><description>This small path leads steeply up to one of the many mountain peaks. It appears to have been well traveled.</description><up><vnum>1546</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1546</vnum><title>Mountain Peak</title><description>From this mountain peak there is a clear view of the rough terrain below. This peak is in the middle of the westen foothills. Far to the north, a great river runs to the east, then turns south. There is a bridge that crosses the river directly to the east of this peak. Glimpses of the Breezy Cliffs can be seen across the river to the northeast.</description><east><vnum>1523</vnum></east><down><vnum>1545</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1547</vnum><title>Nearing A Mountain Peak</title><description>This small path leads steeply up to one of the many mountain peaks. It appears to have been well traveled.</description><south><vnum>1663</vnum></south><up><vnum>1548</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1548</vnum><title>Mountain Peak</title><description>From this mountain peak there is a clear view of the rough terrain below. To the south, the Breezy Cliffs wedge detween two rivers that run mostly north to south. Glipses of the highlands can be seen to the west across one of the rivers. To the east, across the other river, are the eastern foothill.</description><down><vnum>1547</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1549</vnum><title>Riverbed</title><description>There is no current in the water here, but the sound of a nearby rapids can be heard of to the east. There is a small and steep trail leading up the mountainside to the northeast.</description><east><vnum>1550</vnum></east><northwest><vnum>1518</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1550</vnum><title>Riverbed</title><description>There is little current in the water here and the sounds of nearby rapids fill the air. A few underwater plants have grown near the middle of canyon while the calmer water near the riveredge is lifeless.</description><east><vnum>1573</vnum></east><west><vnum>1549</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1551</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The river below here is fairly calm. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A quiet breeze blows towards the northeast.</description><north><vnum>1539</vnum></north><down><vnum>1573</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1552</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1552</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is swift. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are two distint winds blowing here. One toward the east and the other to the north.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><west><vnum>1539</vnum></west><north><vnum>1553</vnum></north><down><vnum>1574</vnum></down><southwest><vnum>1551</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1553</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is swift. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are is a strong wind blowing to the northwest.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1615</vnum></east><west><vnum>1538</vnum></west><north><vnum>1668</vnum></north><south><vnum>1552</vnum></south><down><vnum>1578</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1554</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1554</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is fairly swift. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are is a brisk wind blowing to the north.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1668</vnum></east><west><vnum>1521</vnum></west><south><vnum>1538</vnum></south><down><vnum>1579</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1553</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1555</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>Two rivers meet below here forming a huge rapids. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are two distint winds blowing here. One towards the east and the other to the north.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1565</vnum></east><west><vnum>1535</vnum></west><north><vnum>1654</vnum></north><down><vnum>1581</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1556</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1556</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is fairly swift. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are is a strong wind blowing to the northwest.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1654</vnum></east><west><vnum>1532</vnum></west><north><vnum>1557</vnum></north><south><vnum>1535</vnum></south><down><vnum>1594</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1555</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1557</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. The wind seems to be blowing off to the north.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1656</vnum></east><south><vnum>1556</vnum></south><down><vnum>1595</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1558</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>Two rivers meet below here forming a huge rapids. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are two distint winds blowing here. One towards the northwest and the other to the northeast.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1657</vnum></east><west><vnum>1534</vnum></west><north><vnum>1651</vnum></north><down><vnum>1596</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1608</vnum></northeast><northwest><vnum>1559</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1559</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below looks relatively weak. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A quiet breeze seems to be blowing towards the west.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1651</vnum></east><west><vnum>1560</vnum></west><north><vnum>1644</vnum></north><south><vnum>1534</vnum></south><down><vnum>1601</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1558</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1560</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below looks very weak. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A breeze seems to be blowing off to the southwest.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1559</vnum></east><west><vnum>1640</vnum></west><north><vnum>1642</vnum></north><south><vnum>1533</vnum></south><down><vnum>1602</vnum></down><southwest><vnum>1561</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1561</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is fairly swift. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are is a brisk wind blowing to the west.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1533</vnum></east><west><vnum>1562</vnum></west><north><vnum>1640</vnum></north><south><vnum>1531</vnum></south><down><vnum>1603</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1560</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1562</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below looks to be swift. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are is a distinct wind blowing to the northwest.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1561</vnum></east><north><vnum>1629</vnum></north><south><vnum>1530</vnum></south><down><vnum>1604</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1563</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1563</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below appears to be very strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A strong wind is blowing to the north.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1629</vnum></east><north><vnum>1564</vnum></north><down><vnum>1605</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1562</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1564</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The river below is an raging rapids. The noise of the rushing water seems quieter than it should be. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There air here is perfectly still, but wisps of clouds are circling overhead.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1639</vnum></east><south><vnum>1563</vnum></south><down><vnum>1606</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1565</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below appears to be very strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A strong wind is blowing towards the east.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1669</vnum></east><west><vnum>1555</vnum></west><north><vnum>1655</vnum></north><south><vnum>1667</vnum></south><down><vnum>1582</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1566</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A steady wind is blowing towards the northeast.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><north><vnum>1659</vnum></north><south><vnum>1671</vnum></south><down><vnum>1584</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1567</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1567</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A steady wind is blowing towards the northeast.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><west><vnum>1659</vnum></west><north><vnum>1665</vnum></north><down><vnum>1585</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1568</vnum></northeast><southwest><vnum>1566</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1568</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>There are two rivers below coming together to form a rapids. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There are two very distinct winds in the air. One is blowing northward while the other is clearly blowing to the southeast.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1678</vnum></east><west><vnum>1665</vnum></west><down><vnum>1586</vnum></down><southwest><vnum>1567</vnum></southwest><southeast><vnum>1570</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1569</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The river below is an raging rapids but the sounds of the rushing water seem quieter than usual. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There air here is perfectly still, but wisps of clouds seem to be moving upward into the sky.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1632</vnum></east><down><vnum>1592</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1570</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below is strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A harsh wind is blowing off to the east.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1571</vnum></east><north><vnum>1678</vnum></north><down><vnum>1587</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1568</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1571</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below appears to be very strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. Gusts of wind periodically blow off to the east.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1572</vnum></east><west><vnum>1570</vnum></west><north><vnum>1636</vnum></north><down><vnum>1588</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1572</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The river below is a rapids but the sounds of the rushing water seem quieter than it should be. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. There air here is perfectly still, but wisps of clouds seem to be rotating about themselves.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><west><vnum>1571</vnum></west><north><vnum>1685</vnum></north><down><vnum>1589</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1573</vnum><title>Riverbed</title><description>The current here is swift. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><west><vnum>1550</vnum></west><up><vnum>1551</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1574</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1574</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is very strong. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable. A small stream breaks off from the river to the southwest.</description><east><vnum>1575</vnum></east><north><vnum>1578</vnum></north><up><vnum>1552</vnum></up><southwest><vnum>1573</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1575</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is very swift. The river is inside the mountain and completely sourrounded by rock.</description><west><vnum>1574</vnum></west><southeast><vnum>1576</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1576</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is swift. The river is inside the mountain and completely sourrounded by rock.</description><south><vnum>1577</vnum></south><northwest><vnum>1575</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1577</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is very calm as the river flows out of the mountainside to the south.</description><north><vnum>1576</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1578</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is very strong. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><south><vnum>1574</vnum></south><up><vnum>1553</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1579</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1579</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current of the river is strong here. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><north><vnum>1580</vnum></north><up><vnum>1554</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1578</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1580</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current of the river is strong here. There is a large bridge spanning over the canyon above. It does not look possible to climb up to it.</description><north><vnum>1581</vnum></north><south><vnum>1579</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1581</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is far to strong to swim against. It appears that two rivers are meeting here and forming large rapids that is pushing everything downstream to the south. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><push><direction>south</direction><wait>10000</wait><message>The swift current of the river carries you south.</message></push><east><vnum>1582</vnum></east><south><vnum>1580</vnum></south><up><vnum>1555</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1594</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1582</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is very strong, verging on begin unswimmable. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><west><vnum>1581</vnum></west><up><vnum>1565</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1583</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1583</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current of the river is strong here. There is a large bridge spanning over the canyon above. It does not look possible to climb up to it.</description><east><vnum>1584</vnum></east><southwest><vnum>1582</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1584</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is strong. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><west><vnum>1583</vnum></west><up><vnum>1566</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1585</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1585</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is steadily flowing down to the southeast. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><up><vnum>1567</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1586</vnum></northeast><southwest><vnum>1584</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1586</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Another river cascades into this one from the north. The current here is almost unswimmable because of the falss. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><north><vnum>1591</vnum></north><up><vnum>1568</vnum></up><southwest><vnum>1585</vnum></southwest><southeast><vnum>1587</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1587</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is swiftly flowing down to the northeast. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><east><vnum>1588</vnum></east><up><vnum>1570</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1586</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1588</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is almost unswimmable as it flows steeply down to the east. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><push><direction>west</direction><wait>6000</wait><message>The swift current of the river carries you west.</message></push><east><vnum>1589</vnum></east><west><vnum>1587</vnum></west><up><vnum>1571</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1589</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here very swift. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><east><vnum>1590</vnum></east><west><vnum>1588</vnum></west><up><vnum>1572</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1590</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Water is gushing out of the mountainside here. The water has cut a great canyon through these mountains but there is no sign of errosion here. There is a small ledge on the north mountainside with a rich patch of soil. The rock around the patch of soil has highlights of deep purple.</description><west><vnum>1589</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1591</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is almost unswimmable as it flows steeply down to the south. There is a large bridge spanning over the canyon above. It does not look possible to climb up to it.</description><push><direction>south</direction><wait>6000</wait><message>The swift current of the river carries you south.</message></push><north><vnum>1592</vnum></north><south><vnum>1586</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1592</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here very swift. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><north><vnum>1593</vnum></north><south><vnum>1591</vnum></south><up><vnum>1569</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1593</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Water is gushing out of the mountainside here. The water has cut a great canyon through these mountains but there is no sign of errosion here. There is a small ledge on the north mountainside with a rich patch of soil. The rock around the patch of soil has highlights of deep purple.</description><south><vnum>1592</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1594</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is very strong, verging on begin unswimmable. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><north><vnum>1595</vnum></north><up><vnum>1556</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1581</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1595</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current is strong as the river winds down to the south. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><north><vnum>1596</vnum></north><south><vnum>1594</vnum></south><up><vnum>1557</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1596</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is very strong as two rivers merge. One river is coming from the northeast while the other is coming from the northwest. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><south><vnum>1595</vnum></south><up><vnum>1558</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1597</vnum></northeast><northwest><vnum>1601</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1597</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current is strong as the river winds down to the southeast. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><north><vnum>1598</vnum></north><up><vnum>1608</vnum></up><southwest><vnum>1596</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1598</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The river is unswimmable to the north as the river cascades over ledge. There does not appear to be a way around the falls and the canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><push><direction>south</direction><wait>6000</wait><message>The swift current of the river carries you south.</message></push><north><vnum>1599</vnum></north><south><vnum>1597</vnum></south><up><vnum>1609</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1599</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Water is gushing out of the mountainside here. The water has cut a great canyon through these mountains but there is no sign of errosion here. There is a small ledge on the north mountainside with a rich patch of soil. The rock around the patch of soil has highlights of deep purple. There is a large bridge spanning over the canyon above. It does not look possible to climb up to it.</description><north><vnum>1600</vnum></north><south><vnum>1598</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1600</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>There is almost no current here. There is a large bridge spanning over the canyon above. It does not look possible to climb up to it.</description><south><vnum>1599</vnum></south><up><vnum>1610</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1601</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current is strong as the river winds down to the southeast. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><west><vnum>1602</vnum></west><up><vnum>1559</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1596</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1602</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Change the title of this room by typing "redit title &lt;new title&gt;".   Enter the description of this room by typing "redit desc &lt;description&gt;".</description><east><vnum>1601</vnum></east><up><vnum>1560</vnum></up><southwest><vnum>1603</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1603</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is swift as the river travles down to the northeast. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><west><vnum>1604</vnum></west><up><vnum>1561</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1602</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1604</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Change the title of this room by typing "redit title &lt;new title&gt;".   Enter the description of this room by typing "redit desc &lt;description&gt;".</description><east><vnum>1603</vnum></east><up><vnum>1562</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1605</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1605</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>The current here is unswimmable as it flows steeply down to the southeast. The canyon walls on either side of the river look unclimbable.</description><push><direction>southeast</direction><wait>6000</wait><message>The swift current of the river carries you southeast.</message></push><north><vnum>1606</vnum></north><up><vnum>1563</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1604</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1606</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Change the title of this room by typing "redit title &lt;new title&gt;".   Enter the description of this room by typing "redit desc &lt;description&gt;".</description><north><vnum>1607</vnum></north><south><vnum>1605</vnum></south><up><vnum>1564</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1607</vnum><title>The Windy River</title><description>Water is gushing out of the mountainside here. The water has cut a great canyon through these mountains but there is no sign of errosion here. There is a small ledge on the north mountainside with a rich patch of soil. The rock around the patch of soil has highlights of deep purple.</description><south><vnum>1606</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1608</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below appears to be very strong. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A harsh wind is blowing off to the north.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1660</vnum></east><west><vnum>1651</vnum></west><north><vnum>1609</vnum></north><south><vnum>1657</vnum></south><down><vnum>1597</vnum></down><southwest><vnum>1558</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1609</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The current of the river below appears to be fairly swift. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. A brisk wind is to the north.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><east><vnum>1661</vnum></east><west><vnum>1648</vnum></west><south><vnum>1608</vnum></south><down><vnum>1598</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1610</vnum><title>Above Breezy Canyon</title><description>The river below does not appear to be flowing at all. The banks on either side of the canyon look unclimbable. The wind is also calm here.</description><nofloor>1</nofloor><west><vnum>1647</vnum></west><down><vnum>1600</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1611</vnum><title>Sturdy Rope Bridge</title><description>This large bridge looks very old. It still appears to be sturdy despite swaying from the constant wind. The bridge runs over the canyon river.</description><east><vnum>1667</vnum></east><west><vnum>1536</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1612</vnum><title>Sturdy Rope Bridge</title><description>This large bridge looks very old. It still appears to be sturdy despite swaying from the constant wind. The bridge runs over the canyon river.</description><north><vnum>1658</vnum></north><south><vnum>1669</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1613</vnum><title>Sturdy Rope Bridge</title><description>This large bridge looks very old. It still appears to be sturdy despite swaying from the constant wind. The bridge runs over the canyon river.</description><east><vnum>1634</vnum></east><west><vnum>1666</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1614</vnum><title>Sturdy Rope Bridge</title><description>Change the title of this room by typing "redit title &lt;new title&gt;".   Enter the description of this room by typing "redit desc &lt;description&gt;".</description><east><vnum>1662</vnum></east><west><vnum>1649</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1615</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>The ground rises steeply up the mountainside but it does not appear to be difficult to climb. The ridge extends off to the northeast while another path leads to the north.</description><west><vnum>1553</vnum></west><north><vnum>1670</vnum></north><up><vnum>1616</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1617</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1616</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The rocky ground here drops off sharply but it does not look like it would be difficult to get down from the ledge. The ridge extends off to the northeast while another path leads off to the east.</description><east><vnum>1667</vnum></east><down><vnum>1615</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1618</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1617</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>The rocky ground rises steeply up the mountainside but it does not look like it would be difficult to climb up. The ridge extends down to the southeast.</description><west><vnum>1670</vnum></west><up><vnum>1618</vnum></up><southwest><vnum>1615</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1618</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The rocky ground here drops off sharply but it does not appear to be difficult to climb down. The ridge extends down to the southeast while another paths leads around various boulders and other rock formations.</description><east><vnum>1674</vnum></east><north><vnum>1672</vnum></north><south><vnum>1676</vnum></south><down><vnum>1617</vnum></down><southwest><vnum>1616</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1619</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is covered with is sharp rock formations. There is a large ledge here that appears to be climable with minimal effort.</description><east><vnum>1658</vnum></east><up><vnum>1620</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1620</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is covered with is sharp rock formations. There is a steep dropoff here that does not appear to difficult to traverse.</description><west><vnum>1656</vnum></west><north><vnum>1686</vnum></north><south><vnum>1655</vnum></south><down><vnum>1619</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1621</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>Countless sharp rocks protrude from the mountainside. The ground rises shaply here. The ridge extends off to the northeast. The rise does not look to be too difficult to traverse.</description><south><vnum>1659</vnum></south><up><vnum>1622</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1623</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1622</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>Countless sharp rocks protrude from the mountainside. The ground here drops off shaply. The ridge extends off to the northeast. The drop does not look to be too difficult to traverse.</description><east><vnum>1665</vnum></east><north><vnum>1664</vnum></north><down><vnum>1621</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1624</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1623</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>Countless sharp rocks protrude from the mountainside. The ground rises shaply here. The ridge extends from the north down to the southeast. The rise does not look to be too difficult to traverse.</description><west><vnum>1660</vnum></west><north><vnum>1625</vnum></north><up><vnum>1624</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1621</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1624</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>Countless sharp rocks protrude from the mountainside. The ground here drops off shaply.  The ridge extends from the north down to the southeast. The drop does not look to be too difficult to traverse.</description><east><vnum>1664</vnum></east><north><vnum>1626</vnum></north><down><vnum>1623</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1622</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1625</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>Countless sharp rocks protrude from the mountainside. The ground rises shaply here. The ridge extends down to the south. The rise does not look to be too difficult to traverse.</description><west><vnum>1661</vnum></west><south><vnum>1623</vnum></south><up><vnum>1626</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1626</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>Countless sharp rocks protrude from the mountainside. The ground here drops off shaply. The ridge extends down to the south. The drop does not look to be too difficult to traverse.</description><east><vnum>1663</vnum></east><south><vnum>1624</vnum></south><down><vnum>1625</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1627</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>A small path here is compossed mostly of small rocks and stones. It leads up a steep rise in the mountainside. The path shows very few signs of recent travels.</description><east><vnum>1642</vnum></east><north><vnum>1641</vnum></north><up><vnum>1628</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1628</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>This small path is compossed mostly of small rocks and stones. It leads from a steep slope in the mountainside off to the south.</description><south><vnum>1640</vnum></south><down><vnum>1627</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1629</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>This small path here compossed mostly of small rocks and stones. It leads from a steep rise in the mountainside off to the east. The path shows very few signs of recent travels.</description><east><vnum>1640</vnum></east><west><vnum>1563</vnum></west><south><vnum>1562</vnum></south><up><vnum>1630</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1630</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>This small path is compossed mostly of small rocks and stones. It leads from a steep slope in the mountainside off to the north.</description><north><vnum>1639</vnum></north><down><vnum>1629</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1631</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is rough and worn. A large ledge extends down to the south. It would take some effort to climb to the top of this ledge but it would be far from impossible.</description><east><vnum>1680</vnum></east><south><vnum>1633</vnum></south><up><vnum>1632</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1632</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is rough and worn. A large ledge extends down to the south. It would take some effort to climb down this ledge but it would be far from impossible.</description><west><vnum>1569</vnum></west><south><vnum>1634</vnum></south><down><vnum>1631</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1633</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is rough and worn. A large ledge extends from the notrh down to the southeast. It would take some effort to climb to the top of this ledge but it would be far from impossible.</description><east><vnum>1681</vnum></east><north><vnum>1631</vnum></north><up><vnum>1634</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1635</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1634</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is rough and worn. A large ledge extends from the notrh down to the southeast. It would take some effort to climb down this ledge but it would be far from impossible.</description><west><vnum>1613</vnum></west><north><vnum>1632</vnum></north><south><vnum>1678</vnum></south><down><vnum>1633</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1636</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1635</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is rough and worn. A large ledge extends off to the northeast. It would take some effort to climb to the top of this ledge but it would be far from impossible.</description><east><vnum>1685</vnum></east><north><vnum>1681</vnum></north><up><vnum>1636</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1633</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1636</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>The ground here is rough and worn. A large ledge extends off to the northeast. It would take some effort to climb down this ledge but it would be far from impossible.</description><west><vnum>1678</vnum></west><south><vnum>1571</vnum></south><down><vnum>1635</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1634</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1637</vnum><title>Mountain Trail</title><description>This small path leads steeply up to one of the many mountain peaks. It appears to have been well traveled.</description><east><vnum>1638</vnum></east><west><vnum>1684</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1638</vnum><title>Mountain Trail</title><description>From this mountain peak there is a clear view of the rough terrain below. This peak is along the north side of the Rocky Highlands. A great river runs from the east to west in the south. Across that river, the western foothills can be seen. To the east, across another river, glimpses of the Breezy Cliffs can be seen.</description><west><vnum>1637</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1639</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>A small trail made of rocks and stones extends down to the south. The rock of the mountain looks very erroded here.</description><west><vnum>1564</vnum></west><south><vnum>1630</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1640</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>A small trail made of rocks and stones extends from the north off to the east. There is a unique rock formation here of eight rocks placed ina circle around a larger, almost cubic rock.</description><east><vnum>1560</vnum></east><west><vnum>1629</vnum></west><north><vnum>1628</vnum></north><south><vnum>1561</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1641</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>The ground here is fairly flat with the exception of a few large boulders are trees. All of the trees that are still alive are clustered around one boulder that has been split in two.</description><east><vnum>1643</vnum></east><south><vnum>1627</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1642</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>Loose rocks and stones cover the ground here. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the south. A calm wind is blowing southward.</description><east><vnum>1644</vnum></east><west><vnum>1627</vnum></west><north><vnum>1643</vnum></north><south><vnum>1560</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1643</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>Loose rocks and stones cover the ground here. There is a small cluster of trees around a large boulder. The faint sound of running water can be heard coming from the south.</description><west><vnum>1641</vnum></west><south><vnum>1642</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1644</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>The ground here is fairly flat and covered with very large boulders. A cluster of trees surrounds on particular boulder. Near its base, there is a large hole that appears to extend down into a cavern.</description><west><vnum>1642</vnum></west><south><vnum>1559</vnum></south><down><vnum>1761</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1645</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>This narrow path runs between two very large mountain faces. The path itself is made of loose rocks and stones that have fallen down the mountainsides.</description><east><vnum>1650</vnum></east><north><vnum>1646</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1646</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>The ground here is made of loose rocks and stones that have fallen down the mountainsides. There are five stones in a row next to the east mountainside. They have been arranged based on their size with the smallest to the south and the largest to the north.</description><south><vnum>1645</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1647</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>The ground here is made of loose rocks and stones that have fallen down the mountainsides. There are nine stones in a row next to the east mountainside. They have been arranged based on their size with the largest in the middle and the smallest two to the north and south.</description><east><vnum>1610</vnum></east><south><vnum>1650</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1648</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>The sound of rushing water can be heard all around. A piece of bloody cloth is hanging from a sharp rock that extends out of the mountainside.</description><east><vnum>1609</vnum></east><north><vnum>1650</vnum></north><south><vnum>1651</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1649</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>A narrow trail leads up a steep face of the mountainside. The trail is made mostly of small rocks and stones that have fallen down from higher up the mountain.</description><east><vnum>1614</vnum></east><up><vnum>1650</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1650</vnum><title>Atop A Ridge</title><description>A narrow trail leads down a steep slope on the mountainside. The trail is made mostly of small rocks and stones that have fallen down from higher up the mountain.</description><west><vnum>1645</vnum></west><north><vnum>1647</vnum></north><south><vnum>1648</vnum></south><down><vnum>1649</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1651</vnum><title>Rocky Highlands</title><description>The sound of rushing water can be heard all around. There are twelve rocks arranged in the shape of a triangle on the ground here. The three edges point twords the south, east and west.</description><east><vnum>1608</vnum></east><west><vnum>1559</vnum></west><north><vnum>1648</vnum></north><south><vnum>1558</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1652</vnum><title>Nearing A Mountain Peak</title><description>This small path leads steeply up to one of the many mountain peaks. It appears to have been well traveled.</description><west><vnum>1675</vnum></west><south><vnum>1661</vnum></south><up><vnum>1653</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1653</vnum><title>Mountain Peak</title><description>From this mountain peak there is a clear view of the rough terrain below. This peak is along the eastern side of Breezy Pass. Further to the east is a great river that is running north to south. Across it glimpses of the western foothills can be seen. There seems to be another peak that might be reachable to the northwest.</description><down><vnum>1652</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1654</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose rocks that have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be heard hear all around.</description><east><vnum>1655</vnum></east><west><vnum>1556</vnum></west><north><vnum>1656</vnum></north><south><vnum>1555</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1655</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose stones that have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the south and east.</description><west><vnum>1654</vnum></west><north><vnum>1620</vnum></north><south><vnum>1565</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1656</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by loose stones and large boulders that have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be heard coming from the west.</description><east><vnum>1620</vnum></east><west><vnum>1557</vnum></west><north><vnum>1657</vnum></north><south><vnum>1654</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1657</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by loose rocks and large boulders that have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be heard coming from the north and west. There is a breeze that appears to be blowing around one particularly cubic boulder.</description><east><vnum>1686</vnum></east><west><vnum>1558</vnum></west><north><vnum>1608</vnum></north><south><vnum>1656</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1658</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by loose stones and large boulders that have fallen down from the mountain peaks.</description><east><vnum>1659</vnum></east><west><vnum>1619</vnum></west><south><vnum>1612</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1659</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose rocks that have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be to the south and east.</description><east><vnum>1567</vnum></east><west><vnum>1658</vnum></west><north><vnum>1621</vnum></north><south><vnum>1566</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1660</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose stones that have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be to the west.</description><east><vnum>1623</vnum></east><west><vnum>1608</vnum></west><north><vnum>1661</vnum></north><south><vnum>1686</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1661</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose rocks that seem to have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be to the west.</description><east><vnum>1625</vnum></east><west><vnum>1609</vnum></west><north><vnum>1662</vnum></north><south><vnum>1660</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1662</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose rocks that seem to have fallen down from the mountain peaks.</description><west><vnum>1614</vnum></west><south><vnum>1661</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1663</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose stones that seem to have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The ground rises slightly to the north and west.</description><west><vnum>1626</vnum></west><north><vnum>1547</vnum></north><south><vnum>1664</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1664</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose stones that seem to have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The ground rises slightly to the north and west.</description><east><vnum>1666</vnum></east><west><vnum>1624</vnum></west><north><vnum>1663</vnum></north><south><vnum>1622</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1665</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose stones that seem to have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the south and east.</description><east><vnum>1568</vnum></east><west><vnum>1622</vnum></west><north><vnum>1666</vnum></north><south><vnum>1567</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1666</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose rocks that seem to have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The faint of running water can be heard to the south and east.</description><east><vnum>1613</vnum></east><west><vnum>1664</vnum></west><south><vnum>1665</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1667</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the north.</description><west><vnum>1611</vnum></west><north><vnum>1565</vnum></north><south><vnum>1668</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1668</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths. The sound of rushing water can be heard coming from the south and east.</description><east><vnum>1670</vnum></east><west><vnum>1554</vnum></west><north><vnum>1667</vnum></north><south><vnum>1553</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1669</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the east.</description><east><vnum>1671</vnum></east><west><vnum>1565</vnum></west><north><vnum>1612</vnum></north><south><vnum>1543</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1670</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths. The faint sound of running water can be heard to the east.</description><east><vnum>1617</vnum></east><west><vnum>1668</vnum></west><south><vnum>1615</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1671</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the north.</description><west><vnum>1669</vnum></west><north><vnum>1566</vnum></north><south><vnum>1672</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1672</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths. The faint sound of running water can be heard to the north.</description><east><vnum>1673</vnum></east><north><vnum>1671</vnum></north><south><vnum>1618</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1673</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths.</description><west><vnum>1672</vnum></west><south><vnum>1674</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1674</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths.</description><west><vnum>1618</vnum></west><north><vnum>1673</vnum></north><south><vnum>1675</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1675</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths.</description><east><vnum>1652</vnum></east><west><vnum>1676</vnum></west><north><vnum>1674</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1676</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>The ground here is little more than a large sheet of bedrock that has been cracked and shifted into small peaks and paths.</description><east><vnum>1675</vnum></east><north><vnum>1618</vnum></north><south><vnum>1677</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1677</vnum><title>Breezy Pass</title><description>Change the title of this room by typing "redit title &lt;new title&gt;".   Enter the description of this room by typing "redit desc &lt;description&gt;".</description><north><vnum>1676</vnum></north><down><vnum>1722</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1678</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There is a cluster of trees around one boulder in particular that is supporting a large ammount of growth. There is a large hole hext to this boulder that appears to lead down into a cavern.</description><east><vnum>1636</vnum></east><west><vnum>1568</vnum></west><north><vnum>1634</vnum></north><south><vnum>1570</vnum></south><down><vnum>1687</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1679</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There are many trees along the mountain side, but many of them appear to by dying. A strange wind is blowing off to the north.</description><east><vnum>1682</vnum></east><south><vnum>1680</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1680</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There are many trees along the mountain side, but many of them appear to by dying. A strange wind seems to be blowing towards the southeast.</description><east><vnum>1683</vnum></east><west><vnum>1631</vnum></west><north><vnum>1679</vnum></north><south><vnum>1681</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1681</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There are many trees along the mountain side, but many of them appear to by dying. A strange wind seems to be blowing towards the west. The faint sound of running water can be heard to the south and east.</description><east><vnum>1684</vnum></east><west><vnum>1633</vnum></west><north><vnum>1680</vnum></north><south><vnum>1635</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1682</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There are many trees along the mountain side, but many of them appear to by dying. A strange wind seems to be blowing off to the east.</description><west><vnum>1679</vnum></west><south><vnum>1683</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1683</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There are many trees along the mountain side, but many of them appear to by dying. A strange wind seems to be blowing towards the northwest.</description><west><vnum>1680</vnum></west><north><vnum>1682</vnum></north><south><vnum>1684</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1684</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There are many trees along the mountain side, but many of them appear to by dying. A strange wind seems to be blowing towards the south.</description><east><vnum>1637</vnum></east><west><vnum>1681</vnum></west><north><vnum>1683</vnum></north><south><vnum>1685</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1685</vnum><title>Rocky Flats</title><description>Moss is growing on the boulders of this part of the mountain. There are many trees along the mountain side, but many of them appear to by dying. A strange wind seems to be blowing towards the northeast. The sound of rushing water can be heard to the south.</description><west><vnum>1635</vnum></west><north><vnum>1684</vnum></north><south><vnum>1572</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1686</vnum><title>The Cliffs</title><description>The sharp cliffs and steep drop offs here are hidden by large boulders and loose stones that have fallen down from the mountain peaks. The faint sound of running water can be to the west. Along the mountain side, there is a large hole that looks like it might lead down into a cavern.</description><west><vnum>1657</vnum></west><north><vnum>1660</vnum></north><south><vnum>1620</vnum></south><down><vnum>1708</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1687</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><east><vnum>1689</vnum></east><up><vnum>1678</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1688</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><south><vnum>1689</vnum></south><down><vnum>1691</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1689</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><east><vnum>1690</vnum></east><west><vnum>1687</vnum></west><north><vnum>1688</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1690</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><west><vnum>1689</vnum></west><down><vnum>1692</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1691</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><up><vnum>1688</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1692</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><east><vnum>1693</vnum></east><up><vnum>1690</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1693</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><west><vnum>1692</vnum></west><down><vnum>1694</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1694</vnum><title>Hollow</title><description>This hollow is very dark. From the feel of the walls, this was originally dug out by pickaxes. There is no sign of recent activity here.</description><up><vnum>1693</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1695</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><east><vnum>1703</vnum></east><up><vnum>1540</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1696</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><south><vnum>1697</vnum></south><down><vnum>1704</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1697</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><east><vnum>1698</vnum></east><north><vnum>1696</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1698</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><east><vnum>1699</vnum></east><west><vnum>1697</vnum></west><down><vnum>1702</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1699</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><west><vnum>1698</vnum></west><down><vnum>1700</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1700</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><east><vnum>1701</vnum></east><up><vnum>1699</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1701</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><west><vnum>1700</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1702</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><up><vnum>1698</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1703</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1703</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><west><vnum>1695</vnum></west><southeast><vnum>1702</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1704</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><west><vnum>1705</vnum></west><up><vnum>1696</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1705</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><east><vnum>1704</vnum></east><northwest><vnum>1706</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1706</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><up><vnum>1707</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1705</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1707</vnum><title>Small Cavern</title><description>This cavern is very dark. From the feel of the walls this cavern was formed naturally and has slowly been erroding. There are signs that several smaller mountain creatures are still living in this cavern.</description><down><vnum>1706</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1708</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><west><vnum>1709</vnum></west><up><vnum>1686</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1709</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><east><vnum>1708</vnum></east><north><vnum>1710</vnum></north><south><vnum>1711</vnum></south></room><room><vnum>1710</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><south><vnum>1709</vnum></south><down><vnum>1715</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1711</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><north><vnum>1709</vnum></north><down><vnum>1712</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1712</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><west><vnum>1713</vnum></west><up><vnum>1711</vnum></up><down><vnum>1717</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1713</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><east><vnum>1712</vnum></east><northwest><vnum>1714</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1714</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><southeast><vnum>1713</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1715</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><east><vnum>1716</vnum></east><up><vnum>1710</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1716</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><east><vnum>1718</vnum></east><west><vnum>1715</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1717</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><east><vnum>1721</vnum></east><up><vnum>1712</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1718</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><west><vnum>1716</vnum></west><northeast><vnum>1719</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1719</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><up><vnum>1720</vnum></up><southwest><vnum>1718</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1720</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><down><vnum>1719</vnum></down><southwest><vnum>1</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1721</vnum><title>Curious Burrow</title><description>This burrow is very dimly lit. There is a thick layer of moss cover the floor of this cave and sound of dozens of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air.</description><west><vnum>1717</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1722</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><north><vnum>1730</vnum></north><up><vnum>1677</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1723</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><west><vnum>1724</vnum></west><up><vnum>1731</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1724</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><east><vnum>1723</vnum></east><northwest><vnum>1728</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1725</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><up><vnum>1726</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1726</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><west><vnum>1727</vnum></west><down><vnum>1725</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1727</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><east><vnum>1726</vnum></east><up><vnum>1735</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1728</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><east><vnum>1729</vnum></east><up><vnum>1734</vnum></up><southeast><vnum>1724</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1729</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><west><vnum>1728</vnum></west><north><vnum>1733</vnum></north></room><room><vnum>1730</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><east><vnum>1731</vnum></east><south><vnum>1722</vnum></south><northeast><vnum>1732</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1731</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><west><vnum>1730</vnum></west><down><vnum>1723</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1732</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><southwest><vnum>1730</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1733</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><south><vnum>1729</vnum></south><down><vnum>1737</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1738</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1734</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><north><vnum>1736</vnum></north><down><vnum>1728</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1735</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><down><vnum>1727</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1736</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1736</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><south><vnum>1734</vnum></south><southwest><vnum>1735</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1737</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><up><vnum>1733</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1739</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1738</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>This cave is very dark and humid. The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the faint sound of running water.</description><southwest><vnum>1733</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1739</vnum><title>Dank Cave</title><description>The ground and walls are covered with a thick layer of moss. The sound of small creatures scurrying about echos through the air with the sound of rushing water. A stiff and damp wind is blowing from the north where a dim light can be seen.</description><north><vnum>1768</vnum></north><southwest><vnum>1737</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1740</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. A dim light can be seen to the southeast. The sound of rushing water fills the dry air.</description><down><vnum>1741</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1768</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1741</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><up><vnum>1740</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1742</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1742</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><north><vnum>1743</vnum></north><southeast><vnum>1741</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1743</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><south><vnum>1742</vnum></south><up><vnum>1744</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1744</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1745</vnum></west><down><vnum>1743</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1745</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1744</vnum></east><southwest><vnum>1746</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1746</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1763</vnum></west><down><vnum>1747</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1745</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1747</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1748</vnum></east><west><vnum>1751</vnum></west><up><vnum>1746</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1748</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1747</vnum></west><down><vnum>1749</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1749</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1751</vnum></west><up><vnum>1748</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1750</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description></room><room><vnum>1751</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1747</vnum></east><southwest><vnum>1752</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1752</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><down><vnum>1753</vnum></down><northeast><vnum>1751</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1753</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><up><vnum>1752</vnum></up><southwest><vnum>1754</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1754</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><up><vnum>1755</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1753</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1755</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><down><vnum>1754</vnum></down><northwest><vnum>1758</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1756</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1757</vnum></east><up><vnum>1758</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1757</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1756</vnum></west></room><room><vnum>1758</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1759</vnum></west><up><vnum>1760</vnum></up><down><vnum>1756</vnum></down><southeast><vnum>1755</vnum></southeast></room><room><vnum>1759</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1758</vnum></east></room><room><vnum>1760</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1761</vnum></east><down><vnum>1758</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1761</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1762</vnum></east><west><vnum>1760</vnum></west><up><vnum>1644</vnum></up></room><room><vnum>1762</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1761</vnum></west><northeast><vnum>1763</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1763</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1746</vnum></east><west><vnum>1764</vnum></west><southwest><vnum>1762</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1764</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1763</vnum></east><down><vnum>1765</vnum></down></room><room><vnum>1765</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>Change the title of this room by typing "redit title &lt;new title&gt;".   Enter the description of this room by typing "redit desc &lt;description&gt;".</description><up><vnum>1764</vnum></up><northeast><vnum>1766</vnum></northeast></room><room><vnum>1766</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><west><vnum>1767</vnum></west><southwest><vnum>1765</vnum></southwest></room><room><vnum>1767</vnum><title>Dusty Cave</title><description>This cave is dark and dusty. The grooves on some of the walls indicates that this cave dug out with pick axes a long time ago. This cave seems to have been long abandoned as the wear of errosion has clapsed many digging sites. The faint sound of running water echos through dry air.</description><east><vnum>1766</vnum></east></room><room><vnum>1768</vnum><title>Sturdy Rope Bridge</title><description>This bridge appears to be study despite swaying in the wind. Strong gusts of wind seem to be traveling out of the cave to the northeast, down to the river, back up, and then into the cave to the south.</description><south><vnum>1739</vnum></south><northwest><vnum>1740</vnum></northwest></room><room><vnum>1524</vnum><title>Aside A Ridge</title><description>A long cliff protrudes from the mountainside that extends from the northwest to the south. A large sheet of bedrock has either fallen or been placed to form a ramp up.</description><west><vnum>1540</vnum></west><south><vnum>1522</vnum></south><up><vnum>1525</vnum></up><northwest><vnum>1526</vnum></northwest></room></TrollAttack>